Edward Bleier Papers
Edward Bleier Papers
- Licensing files
  - Genesis Two/Planet Earth Correspondence (Box 28)
  - George's Auto (Box 29)
  - The Getaway (Box 29)
  - Get Carter (Box 29)
  - Get to Know Your Rabbit (Box 29)
  - Ghosts of Mississippi (Box 29)
  - Giant (Box 29)
  - Gilda Live! (Box 29)
  - Gilligan's Island (Box 29)
  - The Gin Game (Box 29)
  - Girl Friends (Box 29)
  - The Glimmer Man (Box 29)
  - G-Men (Box 29)
  - Going in Style (Box 29)
  - Gole (Box 29)
  - Gone With the Wind (Box 29)
  - The Goodbye Girl (Box 29)
  - Goodbye Lover (Box 29)
  - Goodfellas, 2 folders (Box 29)
  - Good Guys and Bad Girls (Box 29)
  - Goodnight Beantown (Box 29)
  - Goonies (Box 29)
  - Gorillas in the Mist (Box 29)
  - Gossip (Box 29)
  - Grace (Box 29)
  - Graduation (Box 30)
  - Graffiti Bridge (Box 30)
  - Grand Hotel (Box 30)
  - Grandview U.S.A (Box 30)
  - Grasshopper (Box 30)
  - Greased Lightning (Box 30)
  - The Great Catherine (Box 30)
  - The Great Georgia Bank Hoax (Box 30)
  - The Great Race (Box 30)
  - Great Santini (Box 30)
  - The Green Mile (Box 30)
  - Gremlins Two (Box 30)
  - Greystoke (Box 30)
  - The Grifters (Box 30)
  - Growing Pains (Box 30)
  - Grumpier Old Men (Box 30)
  - Grumpy Old Men (Box 30)
  - Guilty by Suspicion (Box 30)
  - Guitar Greats (Box 31)
  - Gumball Rally (Box 31)
  - Gunfight at Comanche Creek (Box 31)
  - Guns of Paradise (Box 31)
  - Gypsy (Box 31)
  - Hamlet (w/Branagh) (Box 31)
  - Hamlet (Box 31)
  - Hammett (Box 31)
  - Hancocks (Box 31)
  - The Hand (Box 31)
  - Handgun (Box 31)
  - Hanging By a Thread (Box 31)
  - The Hanging Tree (Box 31)
  - Hardly Working (Box 31)
  - Hard Rock Café, TV Guide articles (Box 31)
  - Hard to Kill (Box 31)
  - Harper (Box 31)
  - Harry O (Box 31)
  - Harry Potter (Box 31)
  - Have Gun, Will Travel (Box 31)
  - The Healers (Box 31)
  - Heartbeat (Box 31)
  - Heartbreak Ridge, detailed proposal of re-editing for network telecast (Box 31)
  - Heartbreak Ridge (Box 31)
  - Heart is a Lonely Hunter (Box 31)
  - Heart's Desire (Box 31)
  - Hearts in Armor (Box 31)
  - Hearts of Fire (Box 31)
  - Heat, broadcast editing notes (Box 31)
  - Heaven and Earth (Box 31)
  - Heidi (Box 32)
  - Hellman/Stern Project (Box 32)
  - The Hellstrom Chronicle (Box 32)
  - Hell to Eternity (Box 32)
  - Helter Skelter (Box 32)
  - Hendrix (Box 32)
  - Her Alibi (Box 32)
  - Here's Looking at You Warner Brothers (Box 32)
  - Here's Lucy (Box 32)
  - Hey Good Lookin' (Box 32)
  - High Road to China (Box 32)
  - History of Rock n' Roll (Box 32)
  - Hitler's Gold (aka Inside Out) (Box 32)
  - Hobbit (Box 32)
  - The Hogan Family (Box 32)
  - Home Fries (Box 32)
  - The Honeysuckle Proxy (Box 32)
  - Honeysuckle Rose (Box 32)
  - Honky Tonk Man (Box 32)
  - Hooper (Box 32)
  - Hope & Gloria (Box 32)
  - Hotel (Box 32)
  - Hotel DeLove (Box 32)
  - Hot to Trot (Box 32)
  - House of Blues, Live From (Box 32)
  - The House of Spirits (Box 32)
  - House of Wax (Box 32)
  - House on Haunted Hill (Box 32)
  - How Sweet It Is (Box 32)
  - How'd They Do That?, inter-office memo on clearance restrictions (Box 32)
  - Hugo and Josephine (Box 33)
  - Hunters are For Killing (Box 33)
  - Hush, Hush, Sweet Charlotte (Box 33)
  - I Could Never Have Sex With Any Man… (Box 33)
  - I Know My First Name is Stephen (Box 33)
  - I Love Lucy (Box 33)
  - I Love You Alice B. Toklas (Box 33)
  - If Looks Could Kill (aka Teen Angst) (Box 33)
  - I'll Fly Away, 2 folders; includes promo/ratings packet (Box 33)
  - Imaginary Crimes (Box 33)
  - Imagine, full color promotional packet (Box 33)
  - Impulse (Box 33)
  - Incognito (Box 33)
  - In Country (Box 33)
  - Incredible Mr. Limpet (Box 34)
  - The In Crowd (Box 34)
  - Independence Day (Box 34)
  - In-Laws The Frisco Kid (Box 34)
  - Innerspace (Box 34)
  - Innocent Blood (Box 34)
  - Inside Daisy Glover (Box 34)
  - Insignificance (Box 34)
  - Interview with the Vampire (Box 34)
  - In the Dark (Box 34)
  - Into the Arms of Strangers (Box 34)
  - Into the Homeland (Box 34)
  - Investigating Tarzan (Box 34)
  - The Iron Giant (Box 34)
  - Invitation to the Wedding (Box 34)
  - The Iron Mistress (Box 34)
  - Irreconcilable Differences (Box 34)
  - Island of the Alive (Box 34)
  - I Spy (Box 34)
  - It's Alive/It's Alive 2 (Box 34)
  - It's a Living (Box 34)
  - It Takes Two (aka Me and My Shadow) (Box 34)
  - Jack Frost (Box 34)
  - Jamboree (Box 34)
  - James Dean 'Forever Young' (Box 34)
  - Jazzvisions (Box 34)
  - Jeremiah Johnson (Box 34)
  - Jesuits (Box 34)
  - Jesus (Box 34)
  - JFK (Box 35)
  - Krush Groove (Box 35)
  - Joe Versus the Volcano (Box 35)
  - Joe's Apartment (Box 35)
  - Jonny Quest (Box 35)
  - Joy Ride (Box 35)
  - The Jumping Frog of Calaveras County (Box 35)
  - Just Cause (Box 35)
  - Just Tell Me What You Want (Box 35)
  - Just the Ten of Us (Box 35)
  - Kaleidoscope (Box 35)
  - Katie (Box 35)
  - Katie: Portrait of a Centerfold (Box 35)
  - Key West (Box 35)
  - Kid 'n Play Are "A Class Act" (Box 35)
  - Killing Fields (Box 35)
  - The King and I (Box 35)
  - King of Beasts (Box 35)
  - King of Comedy (Box 35)
  - Kisses at 50 (Box 35)
  - Kiss Me Petruchio (Box 35)
  - Klute (Box 35)
  - Knights (Box 35)
  - Knights and Emeralds (Box 35)
  - Knots Landing (Box 35)
  - Krush Groove (Box 35)
  - Kung Fu: The Movie (Box 35)
  - L.A. Confidential (Box 35)
  - LAD, A Dog (Box 35)
  - Lady Hawke (Box 35)
  - Lady Hawke Fan Materials (Box 35)
  - Lassiter (Box 35)
  - The Last Boy Scout (Box 35)
  - The Last Frontier (Box 36)
  - Last of Red Hot Dragons (Box 36)
  - Last Summer (Box 36)
  - The Late Show (Box 36)
  - Laugh-In, 2 folders (Box 36)
  - Law and Order (Box 36)
  - Lean on Me (Box 36)
  - Learning Tree (Box 36)
  - Lee, Bruce (Box 36)
  - Lepke (Box 36)
  - Leprechaun's Christmas Gold (Box 36)
  - Lethal Weapon, 2 folders (Box 36)
  - Lethal Weapon 2, 2 folders (Box 36)
  - Lethal Weapon 3 (Box 36)
  - Lethal Weapon 4 (Box 36)
  - Let's Make a Deal (Box 37)
  - Liberty Heights (Box 37)
  - Life and Adventures of Santa Claus (Box 37)
  - The Life and Mysterious Death of Bruce Lee (Box 37)
  - Life and Times of Judge Roy Bean (Box 37)
  - Life and Times of Molly Dodd (Box 37)
  - Life Goes On, newspaper review of episodes with AIDS characters (Box 37)
  - Life Goes to the Movies (Box 37)
  - Life of Brian (Box 37)
  - The Lift (Box 37)
  - Like Cats and Dogs (Box 37)
  - Listen Up: The Lives of Quincy Jones (Box 37)
  - Little Drummer Boy (Box 37)
  - Little Drummer Girl (Box 37)
  - Little Heroes (aka Pee Wee Football) (Box 37)
  - Little Panda (Box 37)
  - A Little Princess (Box 37)
  - A Little Romance (Box 37)
  - Little Shop of Horrors (Box 37)
  - Living Single (Box 37)
  - Local Hero (Box 37)
  - "Lois and Clark" (Box 37)
  - Loneliness of a Long Distance Runner (Box 37)
  - Lonestar (Box 37)
  - Long Dark Night (Box 37)
  - The Long Summer of George Adams (Box 37)
  - Looker (Box 37)
  - Lost and Found (Box 37)
  - Lost Boys (Box 37)
  - The Lousy Continent (Box 37)
  - Lost in America (Box 37)
  - Love Affair (Box 37)
  - Love Child (Box 38)
  - Love Connection (Box 38)
  - Lovesick (Box 38)
  - MacGruder and Loud (Box 38)
  - Mackintosh Man (Box 38)
  - Mad City (Box 38)
  - Made In America (Box 38)
  - Mad Max (1, 2, 3) (Box 38)
  - Mad Max (TV Series) (Box 38)
  - Mad-Tv (Box 38)
  - Madonna: Truth or Dare (Box 38)
  - Magnum Force (Box 38)
  - Magnum Force (Box 38)
  - The Main Event (Box 38)
  - Majority of One (Box 38)
  - Major League 2 (Box 38)
  - Malcolm X, 2 folders (Box 38)
  - The Mambo Kings (Box 39)
  - Mame (Box 39)
  - A Man and a Woman (Box 39)
  - A Man Called Horse (Box 39)
  - Man Behind the Gun (Box 39)
  - Man in the Wilderness (Box 39)
  - Man Who Knew Too Little (Box 39)
  - The Man Without a Face (Box 39)
  - The Man with Two Brains (Box 39)
  - Mark of the Devil (Box 39)
  - Mars Attacks (Box 39)
  - Martha Stewart Living (Box 39)
  - Martin (Box 39)
  - Martin and Lewis Comedy Hour (Box 39)
  - The Marra Collins Story (Box 39)
  - The Masks of Death (Box 39)
  - The Master Gunfighter (Box 39)
  - Master of the Universe (Box 39)
  - The Matrix (Box 39)
  - Maverick (Mel Gibson) (Box 39)
  - Maverick (Box 39)
  - Max Headroom (Box 39)
  - Mayday: 40,000 Feet (Box 39)
  - Mr. Wonderful (Box 39)
  - Madame Butterfly (Box 39)
  - McCabe and Mrs. Miller (Box 39)
  - MCQ (Box 39)
  - Mean Streets (Box 39)
  - Medical Center (Box 39)
  - Memoirs of an Invisible Man (Box 39)
  - Memphis Belle aka Southern Belle (Box 39)
  - Men and Fire (Box 39)
  - Men Don't Leave (Box 40)
  - Men Don't Tell (Box 40)
  - Message in A Bottle (Box 40)
  - Michael (Box 40)
  - Michael Collins (Box 40)
  - Michael Crawford: Music of the Night (Box 40)
  - Mickey Blue Eyes (Box 40)
  - Bette Midler: Divine Madness (Box 40)
  - Midnight Caller (Box 40)
  - Midnight in the Garden of Good and Evil (Box 40)
  - The Mikado (Box 40)
  - A Midsummer in Night's Sex Comedy (Box 40)
  - Mike's Murder (Box 40)
  - The Miracle of Our Lady of Fatima (Box 40)
  - Les Miserables (Box 40)
  - The Mission (Box 40)
  - Mister Roberts (Box 40)
  - Misty (Box 40)
  - Mom and Dad Save the World (Box 40)
  - Money Men (Box 40)
  - Monkey-ed Movies (Box 40)
  - Monolith (Box 40)
  - Monty Python (Box 40)
  - The Morning After (Box 40)
  - Mortal Kombat (Box 40)
  - Mosquito Coast (Box 40)
  - Mother's Day on Walton Mountain (Box 40)
  - Movie, Movie (Box 40)
  - Moving (Box 40)
  - Mr. Mike's Mondo Video (Box 40)
  - Mrs. R (Box 40)
  - Mr. Wonderful (Box 40)
  - Muhammad Ali: The Whole Story (Box 41)
  - Murder at 1600 (Box 41)
  - Murder in Mississippi (Box 41)
  - Murder in the First (Box 41)
  - Murphy Brown (Box 41)
  - The Music Box (Box 41)
  - Music Man (Box 41)
  - My Blue Heaven (Box 41)
  - My Dog Skip (Box 41)
  - My Fair Lady (Box 41)
  - My Favorite Martian (Box 41)
  - My Fellow Americans (Box 41)
  - My Giant (Box 41)
  - My Sister Sam (Box 41)
  - Mystic Warrior (Box 41)
  - My Summer Vacation (Box 41)
  - Napoleon and Josephine (Box 41)
  - National Lampoon's Christmas Vacation, 2 folders (Box 41)
  - National Lampoon's European Vacation (Box 41)
  - National Lampoon's Vacation, 2 folders (Box 41)
  - The National Secret (Box 41)
  - Natural Born Killers (Box 41)
  - The Negotiator (Box 42)
  - Nestor (Box 42)
  - Never Say Never Again (Box 42)
  - Neverending Story (Box 42)
  - The New Age (Box 42)
  - New Jack City (Box 42)
  - The New Land (Box 42)
  - The New Maverick (Box 42)
  - New York, NY (Box 42)
  - Next of Kin (Box 42)
  - The Next to Last Train Ride (Box 42)
  - Nichols (Box 42)
  - Night Breed (Box 42)
  - Night Court (Box 42)
  - Night Full of Rain (Box 42)
  - Nightingales (Box 42)
  - Night Moves (Box 42)
  - Night of the Shooting Stars (Box 42)
  - Night Shift (Box 42)
  - Nikita (Box 42)
  - The Ninth Configuration (Box 42)
  - Noah's Animals (Box 42)
  - None But the Brave (Box 42)
  - No Nukes (Box 42)
  - North and South 1, 2, and 3 (Box 42)
  - North Star (Box 42)
  - Nostradamus (The Man Who Saw Tomorrow) (Box 43)
  - Nothing But Trouble (Box 43)
  - Not With My Wife You Don't (Box 43)
  - Nowhere Man (Box 43)
  - The Nun's Story (Box 43)
  - The Nutcracker, George Balanchine's (Box 43)
  - Nutcracker Ballet (Box 43)
  - Nutcracker: Money, Madness, Murder (Box 43)
  - Nutcracker Prince (Box 43)
  - Nuts!, 2 folders (Box 43)
  - Ode to Billy Joe (Box 43)
  - Of Unknown Origin (Box 43)
  - O'Hara (Box 43)
  - Of Men and Women (Box 43)
  - Oh God (Box 43)
  - Oh, God / Oh, God 2 / Oh, God 3 (Box 43)
  - Old Man and the Sea (Box 43)
  - Oliver Twist (Box 43)
  - O! Lucky Man (Box 43)
  - Omega Man (Box 43)
  - Omen 4 (Box 43)
  - Once Upon a Time in America (Box 43)
  - On Deadly Ground (Box 43)
  - One Crazy Summer (Box 43)
  - One Hundred Eighty Seven (Box 44)
  - One Million Years B.C. (Box 44)
  - One on One / Outlaw Blues (Box 44)
  - One on One / Outlaw Blues (Box 44)
  - One Trick Pony (Box 44)
  - On Moonlight Bay (Box 44)
  - On Tour (Box 44)
  - Operation Daybreak aka Prince of Freedom/Hangman Must Die (Box 44)
  - Operation Pacific (Box 44)
  - Orwell (Box 44)
  - Osmosis Jones (Box 44)
  - Other People's Money (Box 44)
  - Our House (Box 44)
  - Our Time (Box 44)
  - Outbreak (Box 44)
  - Out for Justice (Box 44)
  - Outland (Box 44)
  - Outlaw Josey Wales (Box 44)
  - Outlaw Josey Wales (Box 44)
  - The Outsider (Box 44)
  - The Outside Woman (Box 45)
  - Over the Edge (Box 45)
  - Over the Top (Box 45)
  - Oxford Blues (Box 45)
  - Ozzie and Harriet (Box 45)
  - Pajama Game (Box 45)
  - Pale Rider, 2 folders (Box 45)
  - Paradise (Box 45)
  - Passenger 57 (Box 45)
  - A Passover Seder (Box 45)
  - The Patriots (Box 45)
  - Payback (aka Parker) (Box 45)
  - Pearl (Box 45)
  - Pee-Wee's Big Adventure (Box 45)
  - Pelican Brief (Box 45)
  - The People's Court (Box 45)
  - The Perfect Murder (Box 45)
  - Perfect Storm (Box 46)
  - Perfect Strangers (Box 46)
  - A Perfect World (Box 46)
  - Personal Best (Box 46)
  - Peter Gunn (Box 46)
  - Picasso Summer (Box 46)
  - A Piece of the Action (Box 46)
  - Pink Cadillac (Box 46)
  - Pinocchio's Christmas (Box 46)
  - The Pirates of Penzance (Box 46)
  - Planet Earth (Box 46)
  - Planet Hollywood, Live From (Box 46)
  - Plunderers (Box 46)
  - Pocket Money (Box 46)
  - Point of No Return (Box 46)
  - Pokemon (Box 46)
  - Police Academy 7 (Box 46)
  - Police Academy 6 (Box 46)
  - Police Academy 5 (Box 46)
  - Police Academy 4 (Box 46)
  - Police Academy 3 (Box 46)
  - Police Academy 2 (Box 47)
  - Police Academy (Box 47)
  - Poltergeist (Box 47)
  - Portnoy's Complaint (Box 47)
  - Poseidon Adventure (Box 47)
  - The Possessed (Box 47)
  - The Postman (Box 47)
  - The Power of One (Box 47)
  - Practical Magic (Box 47)
  - Presumed Innocent (Box 47)
  - Priest's Wife (Box 47)
  - Prince and the Pauper (Box 47)
  - Prince of the City (Box 47)
  - Print the Legend: Life and Times of Ford and Wayne (Box 47)
  - Prisoner of Second Ave (Box 47)
  - Private Benjamin, 2 folders (Box 47)
  - Promises in the Dark (Box 47)
  - The Proprietor (Box 47)
  - The Protector (Box 47)
  - Protocol (Box 47)
  - PT 109 (Box 47)
  - Pure Country (Box 47)
  - Purple Rain (Box 47)
  - Purple Rain (Box 48)
  - Quest for Camelot (Box 48)
  - Quick Change (Box 48)
  - Quigley Down Under (Box 48)
  - Rabbit Hill (Box 48)
  - Rabbit Run (Box 48)
  - The Race to Save 100 Years (Box 48)
  - Rachel, Rachel (Box 48)
  - Rafferty and the Highway Hustlers (Box 48)
  - Rage (Box 48)
  - Rainbow Brite (Box 48)
  - Rainbow Thief (Box 48)
  - Rain People (Box 48)
  - Ransom (Box 48)
  - Rapa Nui (Box 48)
  - Rap Attack (Box 48)
  - Ratboy (Box 48)
  - Razorback (Box 48)
  - Ready to Rumble (Box 48)
  - The Really Big Family (Box 48)
  - Real People (Box 48)
  - Rebel With a Cause (Box 48)
  - Rebel Without a Cause 2, 2 folders (Box 48)
  - Reckless Kelly (Box 48)
  - The Recruit (Box 49)
  - Red Monarch (Box 49)
  - Red Sun (Box 49)
  - Replacements (Box 49)
  - Return of the King (Box 49)
  - Return to Salem's Lot (Box 49)
  - Return to Savage Beach (Box 49)
  - Revelations (Box 49)
  - Reversal of Fortune (Box 49)
  - Revolution (Box 49)
  - Richie Rich (Box 49)
  - Richie Rich (Cartoon) (Box 49)
  - Ricochet (Box 49)
  - The Right Stuff (Box 49)
  - Right to Kill (Box 49)
  - Rio Bravo (Box 49)
  - Rifleman (Box 49)
  - Risky Business (Box 49)
  - The Ritz (Box 49)
  - Road Warrior (Mad Max 2), 2 folders (Box 50)
  - Robin Hood, The New Adventures Of (Box 50)
  - Robin Hood: Prince of Thieves (Box 50)
  - Roc (Box 50)
  - Rocco and His Brothers (Box 50)
  - Roger and Me (Box 50)
  - Roll-Over (Box 50)
  - Romeo Must Die (Box 50)
  - Ricochet (Box 50)
  - The Rookie (Box 50)
  - A Room With A View (Box 50)
  - Roots 1 & 2 (Box 50)
  - Roots
    - Correspondence (Box 50)
    - Reviews and publicity (Box 50)
  - Roots 2 (Box 50)
  - Roses Are for the Rich (Box 50)
  - Rosewood (Box 50)
  - Round Midnight (Midnight in the Garden of Good and Evil) (Box 51)
  - Rover Dangerfield (Box 51)
  - Rudolph's Shiny New Year (Box 51)
  - Runaway Jury (Box 51)
  - Running On Empty (Box 51)
  - Russia House (Box 51)
  - Saint Ives (Box 51)
  - Saint Mark's Gospel (Box 51)
  - Saint of Fort Washington (Box 51)
  - The Sailor Who Fell From Grace with the Sea (Box 51)
  - Salem's Lot (Box 51)
  - Saving Grace (Box 51)
  - Scarecrow and Mrs. King (Box 51)
  - Scarlett: Gone With the Wind 2 (Box 51)
  - Schatjes! (Box 51)
  - The Scout (Box 51)
  - Scruples (Box 51)
  - The Sea Chase (Box 51)
  - The Seagull (Box 51)
  - The Sea Gypsies (Box 51)
  - Barry Seal Story (Box 51)
  - The Searchers (Box 51)
  - Second Best (Box 51)
  - Second Serve (Box 51)
  - Second Sight (Box 51)
  - The Secret Garden (Box 51)
  - Secrets of the Bermuda Triangle (Box 51)
  - See You In the Morning (Box 51)
  - Selena (Box 51)
  - Sergeant Rutledge (Box 51)
  - Sesame Street: Follow That Bird (Box 51)
  - Seven Days in May (Box 51)
  - Seven Minutes in Heaven (Box 51)
  - 77 Sunset Strip (Box 51)
  - Seven Year Storm (Box 51)
  - Sgt. Rock (Box 51)
  - Shaft (Box 51)
  - Sharky's Machine (Box 52)
  - Shattered Innocence (Box 52)
  - The Shawshank Redemption (Box 52)
  - Shazam! (Box 52)
  - Shazzan/New Adventures of Batman (Box 52)
  - She (Box 52)
  - The Sheltering Sky (Box 52)
  - She's the Sheriff (Box 52)
  - Shiloh (Box 52)
  - The Shining (Box 52)
  - Shiny New Enemies (Box 52)
  - Showboat (Box 52)
  - Showdown in Little Tokyo (Box 52)
  - Sidekicks (Box 52)
  - Silent Fall (Box 52)
  - Simon (Box 52)
  - Sinatra (Box 52)
  - Singles (Box 52)
  - Sisters (Box 52)
  - Skin Game (Box 52)
  - Slammer (Box 52)
  - Slapstick (Box 52)
  - Sleepers (Box 52)
  - Sleeping Car Murders (Box 52)
  - Smile Jenny, You're Dead (Box 52)
  - So Fine (Box 52)
  - Solar Film (Box 52)
  - Soldier (Box 53)
  - Some Mother's Son (Box 53)
  - Something to Talk About (aka Power of Love) (Box 53)
  - Sommersby (Box 53)
  - The Song Remains the Same (Box 53)
  - Sophisticated Gents (Box 53)
  - Soup for One (Box 53)
  - Sour Grapes (Box 53)
  - South Central (Box 53)
  - South Park (Box 53)
  - Space Cowboys (Box 53)
  - Space Jam (Box 53)
  - Sparkle (Box 53)
  - The Specialist (Box 53)
  - Spencer's Mountain (Box 53)
  - Spenser for Hire (Box 53)
  - Sphere (Box 53)
  - Sphinx (Box 53)
  - Spies Like Us (Box 53)
  - Spiral Staircase (Box 53)
  - Spirit of St. Louis (Box 53)
  - Spitfire Grill (Box 54)
  - Splendor in the Grass (Box 54)
  - Springfield Rifle (Box 54)
  - Stalingrad (Box 54)
  - Stalking Moon (Box 54)
  - Stand and Deliver (Box 54)
  - Stand on It (Box 54)
  - Star 80 (Box 54)
  - Star is Born (Box 54)
  - A Star is Born Concert (Box 54)
  - The Stars Fell on Henrietta (Box 54)
  - Starship Invasions (Box 54)
  - Start the Revolution Without Me (Box 54)
  - Stay Tuned (Box 54)
  - Stealing Home (Box 54)
  - Steel (Box 54)
  - Steelyard Blues (Box 54)
  - Ben Stiller (Box 54)
  - Stingiest Man in Town (Box 54)
  - Stop the World I Want to Get Off (Box 54)
  - The Story of Us (Box 54)
  - Straight Time (Box 54)
  - Strangers on a Train (Box 54)
  - Streetcar Named Desire (Box 54)
  - Streets of Bulawayo (aka Dry White Season) (Box 54)
  - Strictly Business (Box 54)
  - Striptease (Box 54)
  - Stroker Ace (Box 54)
  - The Substitute (Box 54)
  - Sudden Death (Box 54)
  - Sudden Impact (Box 54)
  - Sudden Impact, 2 folders (Box 55)
  - Suddenly Susan (Box 55)
  - Summer Catch (Box 55)
  - Summer Girl (Box 55)
  - Summer of '42 (Box 55)
  - A Summer Place (Box 55)
  - A Summer Without Boys (Box 55)
  - The Sunchaser (Box 55)
  - Sunrise at Campabello (Box 55)
  - Superboy (Box 55)
  - Supergirl (Box 55)
  - Superior Court (Box 55)
  - Superman 4 (Box 55)
  - Superman 3 (Box 55)
  - Superman 2, 2 folders (Box 55)
  - Superman (Series) (Box 55)
  - Superman, 2 folders (Box 55)
  - Superman (Premiere) (Box 55)
  - The Sure Thing (Box 56)
  - Surprises (aka 7 Minutes in Heaven) (Box 56)
  - Surrender (Box 56)
  - Surviving Picasso (Box 56)
  - Swan Lake (Box 56)
  - Swan Princess 2 (Box 56)
  - The Swarm (Box 56)
  - Sweet Nothing (Box 56)
  - Sweet November (Box 56)
  - Swing Shift (Box 56)
  - Switch (Box 56)
  - Table for Five (Box 56)
  - Tai-Pan (Box 56)
  - Tales from the Crypt (Box 56)
  - Tango and Cash, 2 folders (Box 56)
  - Target (Box 56)
  - Tarzan and the Lost City (Box 56)
  - Tattoo (Box 56)
  - "10" (Box 56)
  - Tequila Sunrise (Box 56)
  - Terminal Man (Box 56)
  - That Night (Box 56)
  - That's Action (Box 56)
  - Them (Box 56)
  - There Was a Crooked Man (Box 56)
  - Thief and the Cobbler (Box 56)
  - Third Girl From the Left (Box 56)
  - This Boy's Life (Box 57)
  - Thorn Birds (Box 57)
  - Three Kings (Box 57)
  - Three to Tango (Box 57)
  - Thundercats (animated) (Box 57)
  - Thunder Over the Plains (Box 57)
  - Tightrope
    - [General], 2 folders (Box 57)
    - Script (Box 57)
    - Standard and practices (Box 57)
  - Tilt (Box 57)
  - Time After Time (Box 57)
  - A Time to Kill (Box 57)
  - Time Bandits (Box 57)
  - The Time Machine (Box 57)
  - Time Trax (Box 57)
  - Tin Cup, 2 folders (Box 58)
  - Unforgiven, 2 folders (Box 58)
  - Track of the Cat (Box 58)
  - Tragedy of a Ridiculous Man (Box 58)
  - Train Robbers (Box 58)
  - Treasure Island (Box 58)
  - Trial by Jury (Box 58)
  - Trial of Billy Jack (Box 58)
  - Triple Cross (Box 58)
  - Trog (Box 58)
  - Trojan War (Rescue Me) (Box 58)
  - Troll in Central Park (Box 58)
  - True Crime (Box 58)
  - Twister (Box 58)
  - Tobe Hopper's Night Terrors (Box 58)
  - Tom Horn (Box 58)
  - Twas the Night Before Christmas (Box 58)
  - Twenty Years Later (Box 58)
  - Twice Upon a Time (Box 59)
  - Twilight Zone: the Movie (Box 59)
  - Twilight Zone (Box 59)
  - Twister (Box 59)
  - Two If By Sea (Box 59)
  - 2001: A Space Odyssey (Box 59)
  - To Set A Thief (Box 59)
  - Towering Inferno (Box 59)
  - True Romance (Box 59)
  - Turbo (Box 59)
  - Twister (Movie Premiere), 4 folders (Box 59)
  - Turtle Beach (aka Killing Beach) (Box 60)
  - Ultimate Warrior (Box 60)
  - Ulysses (Box 60)
  - Under Siege (Box 60)
  - Under the Cherry Moon (Box 60)
  - Under the Rainbow (Box 60)
  - Up Periscope (Box 60)
  - Up the Sandbox (Box 60)
  - Uptown Saturday Night (Box 60)
  - Up the Academy (Box 60)
  - Until the End of the World (Box 60)
  - Up and Down in Las Vegas (Box 60)
  - "V" (Box 60)
  - The Valley of the Gwangi (Box 60)
  - Vegas Vacation (Box 60)
  - Victims (Box 60)
  - "Veronica's Closet" (Box 60)
  - Vision Quest (Box 60)
  - "Viva Knievel" (Box 60)
  - Wag the Dog (Box 60)
  - Walking on Water (Box 60)
  - "The Waltons" (Box 60)
  - Wanderers (Box 60)
  - "Warhead" (James Bond) / ABC (Box 60)
  - Warm December (Box 60)
  - Warm Hearts, Cold Feet (Box 60)
  - War of the Buttons (Box 60)
  - The Warrior of Waverly Street (Box 60)
  - The War Room (Box 60)
  - Weatherman (Box 60)
  - "Welcome Back Kotter" (Box 61)
  - The West (Box 61)
  - What Ever Happened to Baby Jane (Box 61)
  - What's Up Doc (Box 61)
  - When First in Love (Box 61)
  - When Time Ran Out (Box 61)
  - Which Way to the Front? (Box 61)
  - White Hunter, Black Heart (Box 61)
  - The White River Kid (Box 61)
  - White Sands (Box 61)
  - Whole Nine Yards (Box 61)
  - Whose Line Is It Anyway? (Box 61)
  - Who's That Girl? (Box 61)
  - Why Do Fools Fall in Love? (Box 61)
  - Wild America (Box 61)
  - Wild Bunch (Box 61)
  - Wildcats (Box 61)
  - Wild West (Box 61)
  - Wild Wild West (Box 61)
  - Will and Grace (Box 61)
  - A Will of Their Own (Box 61)
  - Willie Wonka and the Chocolate Factory, 2 folders (Box 61)
  - Wind in the Willows (Box 61)
  - Windy City (Box 61)
  - Wiseguy (Box 61)
  - The Witches (Box 61)
  - Witches Night Out (Box 61)
  - The Witches of Eastwick (Box 62)
  - The Witching Hour (Box 62)
  - With Highest Honors (Box 62)
  - Without Limits (Box 62)
  - Wizard of Oz (Box 62)
  - Wolfen (Box 62)
  - World According to Garp (Box 62)
  - David L. Wolper Presents (Box 62)